LEBOHANG MOKOENA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

My curiosity for web development has enabled me to gain knowledge and experience. Having worked on both Front-End and Back-End Projects till deployment stage. I seek to continually adapt to this ever changing environment and contribute to a dynamic team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DELTA CRANE PLANT HIRE (09/2018 - 08/2019)

Assistant Mobile Crane Operator Render service for the behalf of the company to different clients. e.g (Eskom, Mittal, Natref, etc)

EPITOME CONSULTING (03/2011 - 06/2011)

Roads and Storm Water Field Inspector.

EDUCATION

08/2018 - PRESENT UMUZI

QUALIFICATION National Certificate in Information Technology

(System Development) (SAQA ID 48872)

(In Progress)

2013 - 2015

SEDIBENG TVET COLLEGE

QUALIFICATION National Certificate: Information Technology:

Technical Support (SAQA ID 24293)

(Incomplete)

SKILLS

- HTML 5
- CSS3
- JAVASCRIPT
- PHP
- .NET (C# AND VB.NET)
- DATABASE DESIGN
- WORDPRESS
- AGILE AND DESIGN THINKING

PORTFOLIO



Github lebohang0824



LinkedIn lebohang Mokoena



Websiteportfolio website

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Developed Library System for Umuzi holiday challenge that has been implemented.
- PERSONALITY
- Hard worker
- Self driven